Cesar Augusto Colorado Rojas

+57 314 394 1790; cacolorador@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/cesar-colorado-82466b121/

Full Stack Developer with +10 years of experience designing/implementing web and Full Stack IT solutions for private and public organizations using different frameworks (**Java**, .**NET**, **Angular**, **React**) and architectures (Microservices, Layered (n-tier), MVC, SOA). Passionate for learning new technologies, platforms (mobiles, cloud computing) and lead development teams in new challenges.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Engineer, CareCloud S.A.S (Telemedicine Startup) — 2022- Present

- Maintained the radiopharmacy system of the National Institute of Cancerology of Colombia that was developed by me a few
 years ago, added new hardware, and improved some features.
- Contributed to the development of the control of symptoms of a medical encounter for the SaludTools telemedication system and collaborated on a document generation system in Vue.js

O Tech-Stack: react , Java, Spring Boot, PostgreSQL, HTML CSS, Google Cloud , PHP GitHub.

Dbaccess, Full Stack Engineer — 2021-2022

- Developed a webapp for an US startup application of fintech for builders, that required an automatic document scan system f
 for check the required documents
- Developed the register and business process for a sell home application

O Tech-Stack: react , Java, Spring Boot, PostgreSQL, HTML CSS, Google Cloud , PHP GitHub.

Corporación Agencia Nacional De Gobierno Digital (Government Software Development Agency), Full Stack Engineer — 2019-2021

- Developed and integrated the colombia government's forms generation system with the government authentication system to unify security in government applications.
- I implemented microservices architecture for the first time in a government project to improve the performance of the the colombian government's citizen procedures system and presented solutions for offer it to remote regions of the country without internet connectivity

O Tech-Stack: Angular, TypeScript, JavaScript, Java, Spring Boot, PostgreSQL, HTML CSS, GitHub.

CareCloud S.A.S (Telemedicine Startup), Full Stack Engineer — 2016-2019

- Designed and implemented a radiopharmacy system for the National Cancer Institute of Colombia, that integrates hardware
 and software, automating the process of creating and handling the radiopharmaceutical, avoiding human errors and improving
 efficiency in spite
- I contributed to the design and implemented a new cloud-based system that performs millions of searches and generates real-time background alerts based on press releases and various databases.
- I used diverses technologies and design patterns to develop the real-time alert system for taking medications and medical appointments for the SaludTools telemedication system, and incorporated a payment system to allow patients to pay remotely.

O Tech-Stack: Angular, TypeScript, JavaScript, Java, Spring Boot, Oracle, MySQL, Architecture AWS, HTML CSS, GitHub.

SKIT CONSULTING (Financial software factory), Full Stack Engineer — 2010-2016

- I managed and developed the new system version of the transaction conciliation process of the Caja Social bank to update the 10 years old system and created tests to maintain behavior.
- I was part of the team that designed and developed a system that generates offering services letters for each client of the Caja Social Bank .
- O Tech-Stack: ASP.NET, .NET, C#, SQL Server, Java, JavaScript, HTML CSS, GitHub,

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, C#, ASP.NET, Php, HTML5, CSS
- Frameworks and Tools: Spring Boot, .NET, Angular, AngularJs, React .REST, Git, Docker, Architecture AWS
- DATABASES: Oracle, PostgreSQL, SQL Server ,MySQL

LANGUAGES

English, Intermediate; Spanish, Native.

EDUCATION

Universidad Nacional de Colombia – Bogotá, Colombia *Master in Computer and Systems Engineering, April 2019*

Universidad Nacional de Colombia – Bogotá, Colombia Systems Engineering, August 2011